

Elianis Medina resume



# **ELIANIS MEDINA**

## **TEAM COACH**

#### **PROFILE**

Extremely disciplined and experienced Team Manager with over 2 years in the field of team management who is accountable for growing business revenue through ensuring that sales and account teams are meeting their goals by helping to build and deliver optimal products and services to customers

# CONTACT

PHONE: 300-8828214

WEB SITE:

https://sway.office.com/VyDhrWgsC48bs zK5?ref=Link&loc=play[1]

EMAIL:

elianismedinao5@outlook.com

# **EDUCATION**

Universidad Nacional Abierta y a Distancia- UNAD

August 2022 – Currently studying.

Currently studying Multimedia Engineering. Virtual program, not attached to fixed schedules.

### Universidad Sergio Arboleda – Programa ATENEA

February 2023 - Currently studying

Currently studying a 6-month program on web applications development. Virtual program, not attached to fixed schedules.

#### British council- Programa English Without Borders

February 2023 – Currently studying

Currently studying a 6-month English program. Virtual program, not attached to fixed schedules.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### ASURION COLOMBIA - Team coach

07/07/2021-01/13/2023

My responsibilities as a leader included:

Oversee day-to-day operation.

Monitor team performance and report on metrics.

■ Motivate team members.

Discover training needs and provide coaching

🛮 Listen to team members' feedback and resolve any issues or conflicts

Recognize high performance and reward accomplishments.

☐ Encourage creativity and risk-taking.

■Suggest and organize team building activities.

## **TELEPERFORMANCE - Bilingual supervisor**

10/12/2020 -06/01/-2021

Worked at home, leading a customer service team in an Amazon UK campaign.

# SGS COLOMBIA HOLDING-Consultant

05/23/2016-10/12/2020

Taking phone calls and delivering customer service and technical support to US customers.

# **SKILLS**

- Interviewing job candidates following STAR method
- Preparing, delivering and follow up Coaching sessions.
- Creating SMART action plans.
- Leading team meetings and huddles to drive performance.
- Time management by using online tools like Outlook and

1 - [1] https://sway.office.com/VyDhrWqsC48bszK5?ref=Link&loc=play